airrace.org 2019-12-17

# Reno Air Racing Association Privacy Policies

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Privacy Policy and Legal Notice**

We have created this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice (“Privacy Policy”) in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [www.airrace.org](https://www.airrace.org/). All references to “we” or “us” in this Privacy Policy refer to the Reno Air Racing Association.

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. By visiting this website, you consent and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the collection, use and storage of your information by us. From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this website following the posting of a changed Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the changes.

 **Information We Collect and How We Use It**

  1. Personal Information  
“Personal information” is information that is uniquely identifiable to you, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, credit card number and other personal information that is not otherwise publicly available.

Using certain features of our website may require that you provide us with your personal information. For example, our website may include the following features:

  * Contests/Sweepstakes
  * Surveys
  * Newsletter Sign-Up
  * Mobile Alert Sign-Up (SMS)
  * Contact Us (email)

To use these features, we may require you to provide your email address, mobile number, name and/or address and certain demographic information (e.g. gender, age, income level, etc.). When you give us personal information to use the features above, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of this information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may use your personal information to communicate with you about:

  * your use of any of the features above;
  * new content on our website;
  * new contests;
  * prize information;
  * news that we think may interest you about us; and
  * responses to your questions/comments to us.

We may use your demographic information for in-house statistics, advertising, and marketing audience information.

  1. Other Information  
Even if you don’t use any of the features above, when you visit our website, we may collect certain information about you.

(a) From your Browser  
For example, our servers keep an activity log that tracks all visitors to the website. The information in the activity log does not identify you individually. The information collected may include, among other data: your IP address, your registered domain or home server, time of access, date of access, web page(s) visited, number of clicks, software crash reports, type of browser used, session identification number, search terms, search results, access times and referring website’s address.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and geographic location. We use such data in the aggregate to run internal analyses to improve upon your experience on our website.

(b) Cookies  
“Cookies” are small text files that are stored on your computer and record your preferences when you visit certain online pages.

Our website uses cookies to track your use of the site and its features and links. We may also use cookies to monitor traffic, improve our website and make it easier to use or more relevant to you. If you provide us with personal information, cookies may be linked to that information.

You may occasionally get cookies from third parties with links (e.g. merchandise retailers and ticket vendors) on our website. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our Privacy Policy.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at www.allaboutcookies.org.

(c) Tracking Tags (also known as “web beacons,” “action tags” or “single-pixel gifs”)  
Our website may also use tracking tags. Tracking tags are invisible graphics embedded in the pages of our website that are programmed to collect non-personal information about your use of our website. Like cookies, tracking tags provide overall usage patterns for our website that we use for analysis and to provide personalized services and advertising content.

 **  
Information Collected by/Shared with Third Parties.**

  1. Advertising  
We partner with advertising companies who may use information from cookies and the tracking tags they place on our website to provide you with targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you based on your use of our website and to track the effectiveness of ads served to you. These advertising company partners may anonymously track your Internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond our website. Any information that these advertising companies collect via cookies and tracking tags is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personal information to them through an ad or email message).

If you would like more information about the use of cookies and tracking tags and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiatives consumer Web site at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising.

  1. Third Parties Doing Work for Us  
We may employ other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail, email, and text messages, conducting sweepstakes/contests, prize fulfillment and promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. These outside suppliers, agents and vendors have access to your personal information only as needed to perform their functions.
  2. Third Parties with Links from Our Website  
From our website, you may be able to click on links to third party sites to buy tickets and merchandise and for other purposes. These third party sites may collect information, including personal information. We are not responsible for, nor do we have access to the information they collect. The collection of this information is governed by the privacy policies on the applicable third party sites.
  3. When necessary  
We may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of ourselves, our clients, our users, or others. Of course, we may disclose any personal information about you to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

 **Mailing Lists**

If you provide your e-mail address, the Reno Air Racing Association may periodically contact you with special offers, updated information, and new services. Any e-mails sent to you by the Reno Air Racing Association offer you the option to be removed from the e-mail mailing list.

 **Security**

This website has commercially reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Personal Information collected by our website is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. While we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

 **Copyright Notice**

All text, images, graphics, sounds and software code (“Content”) on this website are copyrighted property of its respected owners, its clients, contributors and its programmers unless otherwise noted. They may only be used for the personal education of site visitors. They may not be placed in the public domain. You may not reproduce, redistribute, publish or otherwise use by electronic or any other means any of the content without the prior written consent.

 **Trademarks**

The Reno Air Racing Association and other trademarks, service marks, brands, product names, designs and logos related to the Reno Air Racing Association and indicated on this website are owned, controlled or licensed by us. They may not be used or displayed without our prior written consent. All other trademarks, service marks, brands, product names, designs, company names and logos appearing on this website are the property of their respective owners.
